{
    "subject": "resource/Olainfarm",
    "predicate": "ontology/industry",
    "object": "resource/Pharmaceutical_drug",
    "human_readable": "Olainfarm is in the pharmaceutical drug industry.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9440107345581055,
            "question": "Is Olainfarm a company that deals with medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9058898687362671,
            "question": "What industry is Olainfarm involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7101727724075317,
            "question": "What kind of products does Olainfarm produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.688491702079773,
            "question": "What are some potential challenges facing Olainfarm's industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5719481706619263,
            "question": "Give an example of a product Olainfarm might manufacture."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5356540679931641,
            "question": "What role does regulation play in Olainfarm's business?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45831775665283203,
            "question": "Does Olainfarm sell its products directly to consumers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41129443049430847,
            "question": "What is the primary focus of Olainfarm's operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4018319249153137,
            "question": "Could Olainfarm be involved in research and development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34534311294555664,
            "question": "How might advancements in technology impact Olainfarm?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Olainfarm is in the pharmaceutical drug industry.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8095_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Olainfarm be involved in research and development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8095_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary focus of Olainfarm's operations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8095_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Olainfarm sell its products directly to consumers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8095_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8095_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's my evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information that support the statement that Olainfarm is in the pharmaceutical drug industry. For example, they mention that Olainfarm develops, manufactures and distributes FDF products for treatment in various therapeutic areas such as Oncology, Neurology, Cardiology, and Anti-diabetes. Additionally, they describe Olainfarm\u2019s extensive product range including medications for cardiovascular health and other key areas of public health."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}